Okay.
Uh really don't have anything of
injury-wise to give you yet. I mean
Wanya's did not look good. Um
so
Um but I'll we'll be able to get you
that later as we go.
Um
Uh
listen, it was a great atmosphere for a
football game. I
the fans were phenomenal.
Um
we came up short obviously.
Uh need to
Sorry, coach.
There we go. Sorry about that.
All right.
Um so I need to make sure that I give
the guys an opportunity on those those
fourth downs to
to make plays, take full responsibility
for that.
Um thought we could muster something up
there and
and uh I knew points were were
important. So
Um but that's uh
my responsibility to make sure those
work.
And then
um
Uh
you know, the the obvious is we we've
had a
too many drops. You got to take care of
that.
Um I'm not sure where these came from.
We were catching the ball pretty good
there
till uh last couple couple games. So
we've got to go back to that and make
sure we're we're done. These are great
players that are
that that have had some drops and
quarterback I know would like to have a
couple of those
throws back. Um but we've got to start
making those kind of plays offensively.
And defensively I I thought again the
second half of the game
uh we played really really good sound
football and made plays.
Um we're able to put the ball back into
the offense's hands.
And then special teams I thought they
did a good job, too. So
uh with that time, George.
We'll go first to Jesse Newell. Go
ahead, Jesse.
Hey, so I'll have follow-up to Hey,
Andy. I I want to ask you about the
fourth and one. Can you just go over
what you were trying to do there? It
looked like you were trying to get a
Hollywood out in the flat there, but can
you just go over uh your intentions on
that one? Yeah, so Jesse, we we thought
we had a good play. Um
Um some of the going for fourth is you
you've got to you got to feel what
you've got and
we thought we had a good one for him and
and you're seeing that right. It was the
throw to Hollywood. So
And great. And right after the game you
uh you said going for it in hindsight
was wrong. I just wonder after further
reflection
um you know, leaving Patrick Mahomes out
there on a fourth and one, how you feel
about that decision now a few hours
later, you know, having a few hours to
think about it.
Well, listen, I mean I I
we've been so good in that area
um
whether it was run or or pass. And so
I felt we were in a good position. I
thought we had a good play.
Um again, I thought it was the right
thing to do then. I
I I this is terrible to say in a
situation like this cuz we didn't win
and we didn't uh
get that, but I would probably do that
same thing again.
Um
But I also know when you don't get them
it can be a problem and especially when
they're in that field goal range area.
Very aware of that.
Uh but again, I thought the risk reward
was
was right for that time.
>> [clears throat]
>> Uh it
slapped me in the face though. So, it
didn't go that way.
We'll go next to Pete Sweeney.
Uh coach, about 17 years ago in 2008,
you guys needed help from two teams in
in week 17 and and everything kind of
broke your way and that team went to the
NFC title, I guess.
Uh how do tales like that, maybe, you
know, with your own experience and then
maybe other teams help in in just
keeping the faith and keeping the team
motivated?
Yeah, I mean, you hate for it to come
down to that, Pete.
Um but I I
have learned over the years that
anything's possible.
So, I I mean, I communicated that to the
guys. They were they were down in the
dumps after the game. I mean, that's
They they put their heart and soul into
that thing and
uh we came up short. So, but at the same
time, there's the
you know, there's a
way you've got to pick yourself up and
get yourself going again. And
um hope is always a
uh a good motivator there. So,
um
yeah, I think our guys realize that.
I mentioned it to them after after the
game.
>> [clears throat]
>> Not that that's what they wanted to hear
at that particular time. They're still
very upset about
what was what just went on. You know,
they wanted to wanted to win
[clears throat] that game, obviously.
We'll go next to Matt Derrick.
Hey, coach. Um kind of maybe following
up on last week a little bit. What went
into the thought process of having Wanya
on the left side and Jaylen on the right
and and ultimately even even having
Essay come in and play on the left. And
is that the plan probably going forward
as well?
Well, Matt, um
we had you know, you saw the matchups
and all that. So, we always take
matchups into mind.
Um but also
um
you know, where the player is
comfortable, too. So, that's what we
felt
was right. I can't tell you if that'll
be the case this week.
Um we'll see how things go in game plan
part of it.
But
it um
you know, with the exception of the
pressure on the fourth and one, we had
there was some pretty good things that
um
you know, that I thought we did uh
there. But 51 got us a little bit on
that fourth and one to where we want to
go with the ball, but
other than that, it was uh
you know,
I I thought they were
they were respectable job.
And you know, obviously one of the big
plays on that that touchdown drive the
Texans had was that Noah Williams
holding call.
Uh
what did you think of that? Cuz
obviously the it seems like the
the third-party reaction is that that
was not really a holding call.
I think my reaction probably to it said
it all.
Uh that
I mean, you know,
we'll just leave it at that. You can go
back and look at the tape.
I'm sure you have, Matt. Thanks, coach.
Yeah.
Go ahead, Serene.
Uh coach, I'll have a follow-up. You had
a fourth and five earlier, coach. I know
you went for it on the fourth and one.
I'm just curious where you when you got
the
the penalty that shortened it to fourth
and five. Is there any kind of thought
process there or could you maybe take us
through why why
>> Uh so, there were like there were 5
minutes and 12 seconds, I think, left on
the clock in that area.
Um I I really felt like we had
uh a great play there that we could
we could dial up that
fit into what they were doing
defensively.
You know, by that time you have a pretty
decent feel on what's going on and
uh you know, so listen, I mean, I
thought I thought we were within
striking distance there to take care of
it. Um
It
you know, it didn't work out. I mean,
it's uh
I'm I'm talking to coach about when you
you went ahead and punted. Just did you
give some consideration to going for it
earlier on the fourth and five?
Uh you had the the penalty that
shortened it down. I mean,
and you didn't end up going for it. I
just I didn't know was that a close one?
Was it
Yeah, and
I think through them all. But yeah, I
mean,
I'm I'm not going to tell you
I don't go through it. Um
the one we went for, I felt real good
about. And the one we didn't go for, I
wasn't feeling it. So,
uh but
um
you know,
uh
listen, we
we we had a productive play there or the
chance for a productive play and
>> [clears throat]
>> we just we got to make sure that we take
care of business there. So,
And then just my second one to follow up
kind of on Poulet. What did what did you
see? I mean, he you know, a lot of the
analytics, a lot of the grades say he
had a pretty good day. I'm just curious,
you know, did he exceed your
expectations, live up to them? Do you
think there's even more there from him?
Yeah, Serene. So, after the game, I
mentioned, you know, I was proud of him
because he Listen, he had no reps in
practice for the most part
uh other than just a couple fill-in
things, but
um I I thought he did a
did a nice job for what he was asked to
do.
Uh and we just picked him back up here
and
uh he
again had limited reps, jumps in and I
mean, he's a rookie. So, he jumps in and
did some pretty good things against what
I think is a very good football player.
Thanks, coach. Yeah.
We'll go next to Todd Leabo. Go ahead,
Todd.
Hey, coach. You mentioned the drops and
this is not a team and a bunch of
players who've had kind of drops like
that. In your in your experience,
can you put your finger on, just in
general,
why drops happen? Kind of what if
there's a threat on those? And I'll have
a follow-up as well.
Yeah, it's not it's not a from a lack of
effort part. It could be as simple as
just taking your eyes off the ball to
see where you're going to
to where you want to go in these traffic
throws.
Um
So,
um
uh that can be the case or maybe the
ball's a little bit on your back
shoulder and you got to
you got to squeeze it before you
you finish it, you know, and
and take it uh try to take it up the
field. So, there are all kinds of
things. You it could be part part is the
throw, part is the
just making sure that you look at all
the way into the tuck.
And then uh last night the guys were
pretty devastated in the locker room. We
were in there and you mentioned that,
you know,
um
how about the coaching staff? I mean,
you feel like you need to kind of
cheer everyone up? I mean, there's
there's still four games to go. I mean,
how does that kind of operate around
just the building?
Who does that fall [clears throat] on?
Well, it falls on me, first of all. Um
so,
our guys will be ready. They'll be ready
to go. And uh
um we need, you know,
I think you go through this and
you kind of regather your thoughts and
time is a friend here
for you in that area cuz [clears throat]
you spent a lot of time on this, Todd,
as you know,
uh getting ready for these games and
uh there's a lot of effort that goes
into it and you should feel you should
feel that. If you've put everything out
there and you've come up on the
short end, you should feel a
uh
sense that listen, we we got to do
better here. And
um and that's not a great feeling
normally, but uh on the other hand, you
go back through and you still have an
opportunity to go,
uh that fires you up. And so, you just
need a minute here to
to catch it. Now, we don't have the
players in today. So, they're they're
going through that. We're deep into the
Chargers right now. So, uh as we speak.
So, it's
yeah, that's
that's how it rolls.
We'll close it down with Sam. Go ahead,
Sam.
Hey, Andy. Um Hey, Sam. [clears throat]
A couple things I wanted to ask you just
about
the fourth quarter, you know, comes up
and you guys you guys are tied. You've
been in that situation a ton this year.
Do you feel the same sort of energy, you
know, effort to execution on on on the
sideline that that you do, you know,
throughout the rest of the game? Do you
do you feel any sort of similarities and
maybe why they haven't worked out?
Yeah, listen, I
I do feel it. I I thought there was uh
there was great energy, actually, um
going into [clears throat] that. And
uh
I don't think
I don't think it was an energy thing
that that got us in in this game here.
That's I I felt like the guys were were
into it, were encouraging each other and
it it seemed very positive.
Um
we just had
a couple negative things go wrong. I
mean, that's where I'm kicking myself in
the tail on the fourth down. I mean, we
had we did have some
uh
momentum, if you want to
call it that, but there at least was a
positive positive feel going.
And um so,
and then we didn't we didn't get
try to build on that, but it didn't work
out. So, it
when they don't work, it's not a good
thing.
And then I wanted to ask you about a
very specific play that we didn't ask
Patrick about last night, but the
the play where it looked like it
potentially could have been offsides.
There was there was not a flag thrown.
Um was there
confusion about whether or not that play
was live? And it cuz it looked like you
you had, you know, at least Hollywood
was open down field. Was that a play
that you maybe sense there's a missed
opportunity to to get some yards in one
way or another?
Uh
yeah,
I do.
First of all, I thought you know, I
thought it was offsides. I mean, I think
Yeah.
everybody did at that time.
But, it wasn't wasn't called. Normally,
Patrick when he knows it's offsides, he
hangs on to it and tries to tries to
shoot it down the field as far as he can
get that thing to go. So,
to a receiver. But,
he got a little bit of pressure there
and
late as he was waiting on it. Yeah.
Thank you, coach. That's all we have.